

.NET DEVELOPER

Details

Rzeszów

Poland

myhazbo@gmail.com

Skills

C# .NET

Git

SQL

API

Automated Testing

Frontend Development

Hobbies

Reading or watching about programming, chess

Languages

English

Polish

Ukrainian

Profile

With 8 years of experience developing enterprise solutions, my skills as a .Net developer are finely tuned and ready to take on any challenge.

Not only am I a dedicated .Net developer, but I also have a passion for chess that fuels my strategic thinking and attention to detail.

Employment History

Junior .Net Developer, Ideo sp. z o.o., Rzeszów

SEPTEMBER 2014 - AUGUST 2018

Was working on B2B hotel booking platform.

Responsibilities:

- Backend development(WEB API, WCF, ASP.NET MVC, SOLID, DRY)
- Integration with external APIs hotel providers(REST, SOAP, Web services)
- Source control(GIT)
- Unit testing(xUnit)
- R&D (ElasticSearch, Hangfire, Redis, Teamcity + Octopus zero-downtime deployment)
- Frontend development(html, css, ¡Query, KnockoutJS, ASP.NET MVC)
- Databases(MySQL, MS SQL)

Last year was leading the project

.Net Developer, freelancer

FEBRUARY 2017 - AUGUST 2017

Was working on a big ERP system.

Responsibilities:

- Backend development(WEB API, SOLID, DRY, Design patterns)
- Frontend development(html, css, ReactJS)
- Source control(GIT)
- Unit, integration testing(xUnit)
- Databases(MongoDB)

Finished the entire microservice functionality, fixed a few bugs on frontend application

.Net Developer, freelancer

MARCH 2018 - AUGUST 2018

Was working on a small CRM cloud-based system.

Responsibilities:

- Backend development(SOLID, DRY, Design Patterns)
- Source control(GIT)
- Unit testing(xUnit)
- Cloud(Azure)
- Databases(MS SQL)

Implemented few features, helped with bug fixing

.Net developer, Fabrity sp z o.o.

SEPTEMBER 2018 - NOVEMBER 2019

Was working on big Process Automation system.

Responsibilities:

• Backend development(WEB API, SOLID, DRY, Design Patterns)

- Source control(GIT)
- GIT flow
- Frontend development(html, css, AngularJS)
- R&D(Hangfire, multitenant approach)
- Unit testing(MSTest)
- Databases(MSSQL)

Was working on implementing new features, fixing bugs, code improvements

.Net developer, freelancer

DECEMBER 2019 - MAY 2023

Was working on Dashboard project

Responsibilities:

- Backend development(WEB API, SOLID, DRY, Design patterns, CQRS + MediatR)
- Source control(GIT)
- Frontend development(html, css, AngularJS)
- Databases(MS SQL)

Finished the entire project from start until end.

Software Engineer, Primetals Technologies Poland sp z o.o.

DECEMBER 2019 - PRESENT

Working on a big Process Automation System.

Responsibilities:

- Backend development(ASP.NET MVC, SOLID, DRY, Design patterns, process flow implementation)
- Communication protocols(TCP, OPC UA, MQTT)
- Source control(GIT)
- R&D(process flow implementation, project standardization, .Net Framework
 - -> .Net 6 upgrade, InfluxDB)
- Databases(MS SQL, MongoDB, InfluxDB)
- Unit testing(MSTest)
- Frontend development(html, css, jQuery, Kendo)

Started as Software Engineer and finished as Department Head Deputy and Senior .Net Developer.

Senior .Net Developer, freelancer

MARCH 2022 - SEPTEMBER 2022

Was working on implementing a client library for Clio API

Responsibilities:

- Backend development(SOLID, DRY, Design Patterns)
- API integration
- Source control(GIT)
- Unit testing(MSTest)

Finished project from start until end

Education

Engineer, University of Information Technology and Management in Rzeszow, Rzeszów

SEPTEMBER 2012 - MARCH 2018

- Software Engineering
- Computer networks (CCNA Routing & Switching)